<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<articleSet>
    <article>
        <id>0</id>
        <title>The Plague</title>
        <author>Albert Camus </author>
        <publishDate>2022-05-11</publishDate>
        <content>ADASDASD</content>
    </article>
    <article>
        <id>1</id>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <author>George R. R. Martin</author>
        <publishDate>1996-06-01</publishDate>
        <content>
            A Song of Ice and Fire is a series of epic fantasy novels by the American novelist and screenwriter
            George R. R. Martin. He began the first volume of the series, A Game of Thrones, in 1991, and it was
            published in 1996. Martin, who initially envisioned the series as a trilogy, has published five out of a
            planned seven volumes. The fifth and most recent volume of the series, A Dance with Dragons, was published
            in 2011, six years after the publication of the preceding book, A Feast for Crows. He is currently writing
            the sixth novel, The Winds of Winter. A seventh novel, A Dream of Spring, is planned.
        </content>
    </article>
    <article>
        <id>2</id>
        <title>Rick Roll</title>
        <author>Rick Astley</author>
        <publishDate>1987-07-27</publishDate>
        <content>
            We're no strangers to love
            You know the rules and so do I (do I)
            A full commitment's what I'm thinking of
            You wouldn't get this from any other guy
            I just wanna tell you how I'm feeling
            Gotta make you understand
            Never gonna give you up
            Never gonna let you down
            Never gonna run around and desert you
            Never gonna make you cry
            Never gonna say goodbye
            Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
            We've known each other for so long
            Your heart's been aching, but you're too shy to say it (say it)
            Inside, we both know what's been going on (going on)
            We know the game and we're gonna play it
            And if you ask me how I'm feeling
            Don't tell me you're too blind to see
            Never gonna give you up
            Never gonna let you down
            Never gonna run around and desert you
            Never gonna make you cry
            Never gonna say goodbye
            Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
            Never gonna give you up
            Never gonna let you down
            Never gonna run around and desert you
            Never gonna make you cry
            Never gonna say goodbye
            Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
            We've known each other for so long
            Your heart's been aching, but you're too shy to say it (to say it)
            Inside, we both know what's been going on (going on)
            We know the game and we're gonna play it
            I just wanna tell you how I'm feeling
            Gotta make you understand
            Never gonna give you up
            Never gonna let you down
            Never gonna run around and desert you
            Never gonna make you cry
            Never gonna say goodbye
            Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
            Never gonna give you up
            Never gonna let you down
            Never gonna run around and desert you
            Never gonna make you cry
            Never gonna say goodbye
            Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
            Never gonna give you up
            Never gonna let you down
            Never gonna run around and desert you
            Never gonna make you cry
            Never gonna say goodbye
            Never gonna tell a lie and
        </content>
    </article>
    <article>
        <id>3</id>
        <title>Fight Club</title>
        <author>Tyler Durden</author>
        <publishDate>1999-06-11</publishDate>
        <content>
            Fight Club is a 1999 American film directed by David Fincher and starring Brad Pitt,
            Edward Norton, and Helena Bonham Carter. It is based on the 1996 novel of the same name by
            Chuck Palahniuk. Norton plays the unnamed narrator, who is discontented with his white-collar job.
            He forms a "fight club" with soap salesman Tyler Durden (Pitt), and becomes embroiled in a relationship
            with a destitute woman, Marla Singer (Bonham Carter).  Palahniuk's novel was optioned by Fox 2000
            Pictures producer Laura Ziskin, who hired Jim Uhls to write the film adaptation. Fincher was selected
            because of his enthusiasm for the story. He developed the script with Uhls and sought screenwriting
            advice from the cast and others in the film industry. It was filmed in and around Los Angeles from
            July to December 1998. He and the cast compared the film to Rebel Without a Cause (1955)
            and The Graduate (1967), with a theme of conflict between Generation X and the value system of
            advertising
        </content>
    </article>
    <id>1</id>
    <title>Delete Demo</title>
    <author>Kovalsky</author>
    <publishDate>1999-06-11</publishDate>
    <content>
            Pls delet me :))
        </content>
</articleSet>
